[{"answer": "I'm a private detective.  I was hired to follow somebody for a few days.  A guy called my friend. Insurance fraud", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend's got nothing to do with this.  He came here to get his palm read", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "About", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "What about death", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I don't think the dead much care", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Are you a believer, then", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Will you take the job, Mr. my friend", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The case is closed. my friend. my friend's given us a full confession.  Get your ass back to that place", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You never took a fucking vacation in your life, my friend. What's going on", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Trickery and divinity", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No.  I'm saying they were always fake.  The saints, the messiahs, they were just illusionists", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "They weren't worth a damn", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "If he was so good why's he so dead", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He was the real thing, right", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Stuff", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I wasn't", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Oh, I was going to discover the secret of the universe.  That's why I liked my friend.  He promised me all these explanations", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "He had something.  He showed me how to bend the rules.  A little levitation.  A few fireworks", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " ... no..", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Nobody's better off this wav", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'm here, my friend", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yes", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Lord-of-Illusions.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 26}]